[ED
Happy New Year everyone!
I am Kumi Sasaki of Hyuhizaka46.
I would like to announce each member's goals for the year 2024.
First of all, I, Kumi Sasaki, would like to announce mine.
Ta-da!
I want to do radio! I have always wanted to do radio since my debut. I've been saying that I wanted to do radio ever since my debut.
This year, I would like to do my best to make this dream come true by communicating more and more.
I was told by Sarina Ushio, who has since graduated, that Kumi should be more confident in expressing her dreams.
I hope to make this year a year in which I can contribute to the group.
I look forward to working with you in 2024.
My name is Shiho Kato. My goal is to challenge myself. I really want to challenge myself in various things.
I really want to challenge myself in various things for my future and to lead the group "Hyuhizaka46" more.
I will do my best! My name is Kyoko Saito. My goals for this year are
I want to improve my singing ability.
Of course, I love acting and variety shows as much as anyone else, and I really want to do my best in both, but I've decided to focus on one.
I love singing, so I really love acting and variety shows, but I want to do my best in all of them, but I especially want to improve my singing ability.
I'm looking forward to working with you again this year.
I want to work with animals.
I have three animals, and I love them very much.
I'd like to try my hand at something related to animals. I'll do my best.
My name is Mana Takase. My goal for this year is to try my hand at musicals.
I love to sing, so I want to sing a lot. I've always dreamed of doing a musical, and I'd like to try my hand at it!
I'll do my best!
I'm Ayaka Takamoto. My goal is to make a job out of what I love!
In 2023, I'll be able to do more of what I like and what I can do, so I'd like to make this year a year to connect it to my work. I have found that in 2023, I am able to do more of what I like and what I can do, so I would like to make it a year to connect that to my work.
My name is Mei Higashimura, and I'm looking forward to working with you this year.
My goal for this year is to produce cuteness.
I love cute things, so I want to produce cute sweets and goods.
I would like to produce various cute things.
My name is Mika Tanimura. Here are my goals for this year.
This year, I want to face myself and do my best in everything I do.
I look forward to working with you.
My name is Hina Kawada.
My resolution for this year is
To be a warm person.
I will do my best to become a person who can grow as a human being.
I am Sunao Kosaka.
My goal for 2020 is
I want to enjoy working with the members more.
I would like to laugh with everyone more and enjoy working with them in 2020.
I look forward to working with you!
My name is Suzuka Tomita. My goal for this year is to learn acting.
Last year I performed in a musical, and this year I'd like to expand my range as a human being and a performer.
I will do my best this year, so please give me your support.
My name is Akari Futaba. Here are my goals for this year
I want to work as a recording artist, so I'll do my best to talk a lot.
My name is Hiyori Imagishi. I want to expand my modeling work.
I look forward to working with you again this year.
My name is Matsuda Onoka. My goal for this year is to try my hand at acting.
I'm Hinano Uemura from Hyugaizaka 46. My resolution for this year is to deliver my voice. I'm Hinano Uemura from Hyugaizaka46. My resolution for this year is to deliver my voice.
I'm Mikuuri Takahashi from Hyugaizaka46. My resolution for this year is to be a key member of "Jean! I will do my best to improve my singing and dancing.
I'm Mariy Morimoto. I want to spread the charm of travel.
I really love traveling, so I hope I can travel a little bit.
Haruyo Yamaguchi: My resolution for this year is to improve my voice and expressiveness.
I look forward to working with you.
My name is Tamaki Ishizuka. My goal is to communicate what I like.
I'm Tamaki Ishizuka, turning 20 years old. Hello, I'm Nami.
My goal is to be a person who can show my fashion sense. I like clothes, so I want to be a person who can show myself in the genre of fashion.
I will do my best this year!
My name is Rio Seimizu. My resolution for this year is to give an eye-catching performance.
I love to sing and dance, so I will do my best to make my performance shine even more brightly at live shows.
I am Jouko, a boy. Here are my aspirations for this year. I want to deliver my feelings through my expression.
I will do my best this year to express what I am thinking at live performances and at work.
I am Kirari Takeuchi. My ambition for 2024 is to show many attractions of my hometown Hiroshima.
I am the only Hinanozaka46 member from Hiroshima prefecture.
I made this resolution in the hope that I can convey the charms of Hiroshima to everyone as the only resident of Hiroshima Prefecture in Hinanozaka46.
I look forward to working with you in 2024!
My name is Honkama Hiraoka.
My aspirations for this year are
I want to do my best in Hina-ai and Hina-nari.
This year, I will do my best to become an indispensable member of Hinaa and Hinanari.
I look forward to working with you this year!
Hi, I'm Mizuki Hiraoka.
My name is Mizuki Hiraoka.
My goal for this year is to output. My goal for this year is to output a lot.
I've learned a lot of things in 2023, and I'd like to output a lot this year.
This year, I want to output a lot of it and deliver it to you all.
I'll do my best. Thank you very much.
My name is Kaho Fujishima.
My goal this year is to share my love for Hokkaido.
I will do my best to be a person who can convey the charms of Hokkaido.
I will do my best this year too!
My name is Smil Miyake.
I'm Smil Miyake and I'm going to work hard to get involved in radio and soccer.
I experienced many things last year, and I would like to continue to pursue my favorite things.
My name is Haruka Yamashita. My goal for this year is to improve my talk skill.
I'll do my best. I'm Gina Watanabe.
My goal for this year is to learn how to express myself in my own way.
I'm Gina Watanabe.
I'll do my best to deliver a more powerful performance.
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with Hinotoko46 in 2024
I look forward to working with you in 2024.